Reece Lardy

6023 Lynn Way • Woodbury, MN 55129 651.260.3257 • RJLardy21@gmail.com

Objective

Talented individual with strong communication skills, team spirit, and B.S. in Computer Engineering desires the position of Software Engineer. Bringing expertise in writing full-stack code to support multiple platforms, including web, android, and iOS, and a solid grasp of algorithms, databases, data structures and object-oriented designs.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

May 2021

University of Wisconsin-Madison

• GPA: 3.1/4.0

Experience

Software Engineering Intern

May 2020 - Aug 2020 Bloomington, MN

DispatchIt, Inc.

- #5 Forbes Best Startup
- Worked remotely (COVID-19) with the product and engineering team using Ruby on Rails in order to create a multiple stop order solution for the company
- Duties included regular Agile meetings, using RSpec to write unit tests to ensure functionality, and completing assigned new feature stories

IoT Engineering Intern

Jan 2020 - May 2020

Madison, WI

Flad Architects

- Architected and programmed a complete post-occupancy evaluation solution using LoRa, ESP32 BLE sensors, Google Firebase, Arduino, reported using PowerBI dashboard
- Being able to make design choices as an engineer allowed me to make a higher quality product by using a technology stack that best fit the project requirements

Software Engineering Intern

May 2019 - August 2019

Pearson VUE

Bloomington, MN

- Fixed defects and wrote new features in numerous codebases across our product
- Gave bi-weekly presentations to upper-management about my team's Agile (Scrum) iteration
- Maintained build tools (Gradle, Ant) to ensure builds containing over 100 dependencies succeeded

Skills

- Experience coding with Java, Ruby on Rails, HTML, JavaScript, MySQL, CSS, SSH, Python, PHP, Apache, Swift, Express, and React
- Fluent Spanish Speaker
- Excellent communication skills and great with collaborative work

Activities

Software Development Club Recreational Basketball

Website

Please visit ReeceLardy.com to see the portfolio website I made with a more detailed resume and samples of my side projects